allbloggingways.com 2017-06-30

# Privacy Policy - All Blogging ways

At AllbloggingWays the  **privacy**  of our visitors is extremely very important. This  _Privacy_ _  Policy_ outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how is it used.

This Privacy Policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. You may want to revisit it regularly. You can use this website, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

### **LOG FILES**

We use log files like many other websites. The information in the log files include:

  * Internet Protocol addresses (IP)
  * Referring and exit pages
  * Types of browser
  * Date and time stamp
  * Internet Service Provider (ISP)
  * Number of clicks

All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

### **Cookies**

We use cookies to store information about visitor preferences and to record user-specific information on visits and pages the user views so as to provide a custom experience. In regard to third-party advertisers, All Blogging ways has no access or control over these cookies. You should review the respective privacy policies on any and all third-party ad servers for more information regarding their practices and how to opt-out.

If you wish to disable cookies you may do so through your web browser options. Instructions for doing so and for other cookie-related management can be found on the specific web browsers’ websites.

### **Other**

Users might be asked to subscribe to our newsletter by providing name and email address to receive communication from ABW. We use a secure op-in subscription system and we reserve the right to contact subscribers with information related to this website and blog. Subscribers may unsubscribe anytime and every email delivered will contain an “Unsubscribe” link.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy please feel free to contact us by Contact us form.
